Guide to the Friends of the Museum of Art, Washington State University, Papers 1977-1981
Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections, Washington State University Libraries
Friends of the Museum of Art, Washington State University, Papers
1977-1981
Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections, Washington State University Libraries http://www.libraries.wsu.edu/masc Terrell Library P.O. Box 645610 Pullman 99164-5610 mascref@wsu.edu http://www.libraries.wsu.edu/masc
Friends of the Museum of Art. Washington State University
Cage.890
0.25 linear feet 1 box.
This collection consists of papers and correspondence related to the Friends of the Museum of Art, Washington State University.
This collection consists of correspondence, meeting minutes, and constitution of the Friends of the Museum of Art at Washington State University dating from 1977-1981. The correspondence includes letters to and from the organization, as well as financial reports and meeting agendas, from the files of June Bierbower.
This collection is arranged in a single series by subject and date. The first folder is the Constitution for the organization from 1977. The next folder contains membership lists from 1977-1979, followed by Board of Directors meeting minutes from 1977-1980. The rest of the collection consists of correspondence, beginning with a folder of undated correspondence, and the subsequent folders are in chronological order.
The Friends of the Museum of Art at Washington State University was formed to advance educational and public support for the museum. The organization was designed to work in conjunction with the museum to obtain funding and donations of works of art from sources outside the University.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Marie Moree donated this collection to the Washington State University Libraries in 1983 (MS.1983.18).
Fine Arts Department/Museum of Art materials in the University Archives, WSU Publications collection (WSU 79).
Washington State University--History--Sources
Fine Arts; Colleges and Universities
- Copies of the organization's constitution., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Membership lists., 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes of the Board of Directors meetings., 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence., undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence., 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Transmittal (documentation received with collection)., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)